<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Mei</name>
    <directory>mei</directory>
    <id>842051906</id>
    <description>Play as Mei, a ghost with telekinetic powers.

A new, fully sprited, additional custom character. She controls tears using her psychic powers and grudges her enemies to boost her abilities.

[i]This mod does not add items that allow other characters to use her abilities.[/i]

[i]There are additional assets that can be used for thumbnails, social media posts, etc. in the mod folder.[/i]

[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=879410535]Mei Mod: Red Hearts[/url]
[url=http://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=879757757]Mei Mod: Piercing Tears[/url]

[b]Stats[/b]
[table]
	[tr]
		[td]Damage[/td]
		[td]x0.40 + 0.30[/td]
	[/tr]
	[tr]
		[td]Move Speed[/td]
		[td]x0.8 + 0.10[/td]
	[/tr]
	[tr]
		[td]Shot Speed[/td]
		[td]x0.8 + 0.30[/td]
	[/tr]
	[tr]
		[td]Health[/td]
		[td]3 Black Hearts[/td]
	[/tr]
[/table]

[h1][b]Mechanics[/b][/h1]
Almost every tear effect in the game works with Mei, and some are quite powerful.
Any Red Heart Containers Mei gains are converted to 1.5 Black Hearts.
The amount of tears Mei controls is based on her Tears stat.
The speed at which the tears orbit around Mei is based on her Shot Speed stat.
Mei forms Grudges with enemies she attacks and enemies that get too close to her.
Tears Mei controls are incorporeal and deal no damage until she attempts to attack.
The distance at which Mei forms Grudges with enemies is based on a multiple of her Range stat.
Every Grudge Mei maintains increases her damage, and they fade slowly over time.

[h1][b]Strategy[/b][/h1]
Enemy too far away? Standing still gradually increases Mei's orbit range.
Having trouble hitting enemies? Tap shoot to control the distance of Mei's tears.
Enemies rushing you down? Fend off enemies that get too close by firing in the opposite direction.
Feeling a little weak? Damage and graze multiple enemies for a big temporary damage increase.
Grudges hard to maintain? Each Range Up increases the Grudge distance a lot.
Knockback getting you down? Tap the drop trinket button to reverse Mei's orbital direction.

Special Thanks to [url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/Taitou4ever/]Lord Shaxx[/url] for the thought-provoking concept of multiple orbital rings which led to a bunch of sweet synergies.

[i]yatboim[/i]</description>
    <version>1.80</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Player Characters"/>
</metadata>
